let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which institution released the 14th Emissions Gap Report 2023?",
    answer: "UNEP",
    options: [
      "UNESCO",
      "UNEP",
      "World Bank",
      "WHO"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which state is the host of the Global Fisheries Conference India 2023?",
    answer: "Gujarat",
    options: [
      "Maharashtra",
      "West Bengal",
      "Tamil Nadu",
      "Gujarat"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "As per WHO 2023 Global TB report, which county accounted for the highest number of tuberculosis (TB) cases in the world in 2022?",
    answer: "India",
    options: [
      "India",
      "China",
      "Ethiopia",
      "Pakistan"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which country has pulled out of the Treaty of Conventional Armed Forces in Europe?",
    answer: "Russia",
    options: [
      "Russia",
      "Israel",
      "France",
      "Germany"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which Indian city has been added to the UNESCO Creative Cities Network, in Literature category?",
    answer: "Kozhikode",
    options: [
      "Kozhikode",
      "Mysore",
      "Banglore",
      "Madurai"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which city is the host of World Health Summit 2023?",
    answer: "Berlin",
    options: [
      "New Delhi",
      "Berlin",
      "Rome",
      "New York"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What is the rank of India in the Global Hunger Index (GHI) 2023?",
    answer: "111",
    options: [
      "121",
      "131",
      "101",
      "111"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What is the rank of India in the Global Innovation Index 2023?",
    answer: "40",
    options: [
      "40",
      "60",
      "50",
      "30"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Vajra Prahar 2023 is a joint exercise between which countries?",
    answer: "India and the United States",
    options: [
      "India and Sri Lanka",
      "India and UK",
      "India and the United States",
      "India and France"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which scarce element has been discovered in the Sutlej River?",
    answer: "Tantalum",
    options: [
      "Titanium",
      "Tantalum",
      "Scandium",
      "Lithium"
    ]
  },
];

